A Guide to the Wade Hampton Frost Collection 1880-1938; 1938-1984
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- WADE HAMPTON FROST 6 June 1939, 1 photo portrait B&W 8 X 10 (Box-folder 07-033)
  PORTRAIT PRESENTED AT JOHNS HOPKINS COMMENCEMENT EXERCISES ADDRESS DELIVERED BY W. H. HOWELL
- SUSAN HAXALL FROST c. 1950, 1 photo B&W 3.5 x 5.25 (Box-folder 07-034)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST 1 May 1958, 1 photo portrait mounted B&W 9.75 X 13 (Box-folder 07-035)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST 1937, 2 photos B&W 3.5 X 5.25 (Box-folder 07-036)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST AND SUSAN FROST PARRISH 1937, 2 photos (Box-folder 07-037)
- SUSAN FROST PARRISH 1936-37, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.25 (Box-folder 07-038)
- SUSAN FROST PARRISH; OBITUARY FOR SUSAN FROST PARRISH 1960; 1994, 1 photo B&W 3.5 X 5.25; 1 newsclipping (Box-folder 07-039)
- ARTICLE BY WADE HAMPTON FROST; CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN VIRGINIA HAXALL HARRISON WHITRIDGE AND JACK M. GWALTNEY, JR. 1976-82, 6 TLS; 14 photocopies (Box-folder 08-001)
- GUIDE TO ALDERMAN LIBRARY 1980, pamphlet (Box-folder 08-002)
  PROBABLY SUSAN FROST PARRISH'S COPY
- POEM, "THE GIFT" BY LONA GALE nd, 2 AMs; 4 photocopies (Box-folder 08-003)
- LETTER FROM SUSAN FROST PARRISH TO JOHN GOTT RE: MARSHALL HISTORY 1986-87, 10 AMs; 4 TLS (Box-folder 08-004)
- FROST-WHITRIDGE FUND AT UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA MEDICAL CENTER Dec. 1981-Jan. 1983, 5 ANs; 11 TLS; 4 TD (Box-folder 08-005)
  "RECEIPTS, LETTERS, ETC."
- SUSAN FROST PARRISH MISCELLANEOUS NOTES "n.d., early 1980s?", 28 AN; 2 TN (Box-folder 08-006)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST BIBLIOGRAPHY WITH NOTES BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH AND RUTIZER RESEARCH 1975-77, 9 TD; 13 AN; 6 TN (Box-folder 08-007)
- LETTER FROM FRANK L. HEREFORD TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 1976-85, 6 AN; 35 TLS; 18 TD (Box-folder 08-008)
  "COPIES OF DEED OF GIFT, APPRAISAL OF WADE HAMPTON FROST COLLECTION"
- BOOK COLLECTION OF WADE HAMPTON FROST DONATED TO UVA AND CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN SUSAN FROST PARRISH AND WILHELM MOLL 1976-84, 25 TD; 11 TLS; 1 AN; 9 TNS (Box-folder 08-009)
  "LISTS, APPRAISALS, ETC."
- HANDWRITTEN LISTS OF WADE HAMPTON FROST BOOK DONATION n.d., 48 AD (Box-folder 08-010)
- CORRESPONDENCE AND NOTES RE: WADE HAMPTON FROST CHAIR AT UVA 1974-1985, 4 TLS; 18 TD; 13 ALS; 17 AN (Box-folder 08-011)
- INTERVIEW BY BARRY RUTIZER WITH C. MARSHALL BARTON AND NOTES 1975-84, 19 TNS; 4 ALS (Box-folder 08-012)
  NOTES BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH ATTACHED
- JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY SYMPOSIUM ON INTERNATIONAL HEALTH HONORING ERNEST L. STEBBINS AND ABEL WOLMAN AND CORRESPONDENCE, NOTES AND ARTICLES 1976 Feb., 16 TLS; 22 PD; 5 ALS; 20 AN (Box-folder 08-013)
- THE ORIGINS OF THE FIRST SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND PUBLIC HEALTH AND THE EASTERN HEALTH DISTRICT IN BALIMORE" BY HUNTINGTON WILLIAMS 1961, 12 PD (Box-folder 08-014)
  PUBLISHED BY THE BALTIMORE CITY HEALTH DEPARTMENT
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN SUSAN FROST PARRISH AND ABRAHAM LILIENFELD RE: REED-FROST SYMPOSIUM 1976 Feb, 1 TLS; 1 ALS (Box-folder 08-015)
- PHOTOCOPIES OF TITLE PAGES OF "PAPERS OF WADE HAMPTON FROST" AND "SNOW ON CHOLERA" 1936-41, 6 PD (Box-folder 08-016)
- PHOTOCOPIES OF TITLE PAGES OF HENRY ROSE CARTER'S HISTORY OF YELLOW FEVER, EDITED BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 1931, 5 AN; 2 pp. photocopies (Box-folder 08-017)
  ALSO INCLUDES PHOTOCOPIED NOTE FROM CARTERS TO FROSTS AND NOTES BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH
- NOTES BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH FOR BARRY RUTIZER FOR RESEARCH ON WADE HAMPTON FROST June 1975, 10 AN; 2 TNS (Box-folder 08-018)
  "WHO HE MIGHT INTERVIEW, ETC."
- NEWSCLIPPINGS RE: WADE HAMPTON FROST AND JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND PUBLIC HEALTH 1938-66, 14 photo. newsclips; 1 newsclip (Box-folder 08-019)
- LETTERS AND ARTICLES ABOUT WADE HAMPTON FROST 1939-84, 2 TLS; 10 TN; 1 article (Box-folder 08-020)
  "COMMEMORATIVE ADDRESS AT JHU, ARTICLE ON COLDS, ETC."
- LETTER FROM GEORGE A. AUDEN TO WADE HAMPTON FROST 17 Sept. 1933, 4 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-001)
  PHOTOCOPIES
- LETTERS FROM REGINALD M. ATWATER TO WADE HAMPTON FROST AND TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST Nov. 1921-Sept. 1938, 5 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-002)
- LETTER FROM EUGENE L. BISHOP TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST Sept. 1938-May 1939, 2 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-003)
- LETTER FROM JOHN STEWART BRYANT TO WADE HAMPTON FROST 25 Sept. 1936, 1 p. copy (Box-folder 09-004)
  "NOTE ATTACHED SHOWS LETTER MISSING, 9/7/85"
- LETTER FROM FRANK A. CALDERONE TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 23 May 1938, 1 p. copy (Box-folder 09-005)
- LETTER FROM CHARLES V. CHAPIN TO WADE HAMPTON FROST AND FROM JAMES H. CASSEDY TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST Feb. 1924-May 1961, 6 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-006)
  CASSEDY LETTER OF MAY 1961 PARTLY QUOTES WADE HAMPTON FROST TO DR. CHAPIN OF 1924
- LETTER FROM ANTONIO CIOCCO TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 2 May 1938, 1 p. copy (Box-folder 09-007)
- LETTER FROM RICHARD H. CREEL TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 12 Sept 1938, 3 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-008)
- LETTER FROM HUGH S. CUMMING TO WADE HAMPTON FROST March 1921-Feb. 1931, 23 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-009)
  COPIES MADE FROM RESEARCH PHOTOCOPIES OF BARRY P. RUTIZER
- LETTER FROM HUGH S. CUMMING, JR. TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 23 Feb 1972, 5 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-010)
- LETTER FROM THOMAS UNDERWOOD DUDLEY TO WADE HAMPTON FROST 13 Feb 1938, 1 p. copy (Box-folder 09-011)
  COPY OF LETTER MISSING JT 4-4-97
- LETTER FROM HAVEN EMERSON TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 26 Nov. 1938, 2 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-012)
- LETTER FROM HAVEN EMERSON, W. S. LEATHERS WADE HAMPTON FROST TO HUGH S. CUMMING 1 Aug 1935, 8 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-013)
  RE: PENDING SOCIAL SECURITY BILL
- LETTER FROM J.G. FITZGERALD TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 13 Oct 1938, 2 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-014)
- LETTERS FROM HENRY FROST TO WADE HAMPTON FROST July 1913-Dec. 1917, 51 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-015)
  "HENRY FROST, FATHER OF WADE HAMPTON FROST"
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO HENRY ROSE CARTER Feb. 1922-April 1925, 33 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-016)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO LAURA ARMISTEAD CARTER July 1927-Sept. 1930, 17 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-017)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO HUGH S. CUMMING June 1916-Nov. 1929, 16 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-018)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO HUGH S. CUMMING 8 Aug. 1935, 3 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-019)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 1920-1932, 6 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-020)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH Nov. 1937-Feb. 1938, 64 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-021)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO THOMAS LOWNDES FROST AND NEWSCLIPPING RE: DEATH OF THOMAS LOWNDES FROST May 1922-March 1923, 36 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-022)
- LETTER FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO J. TRIPLETT HAXALL Mar. 1935, 3 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-023)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST AND FROM SUSAN HAXALL FROST TO WILLIAM H. WELCH July 1919-Aug. 1933, 31 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-024)
  FROM JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY WILLIAM H. WELCH MEDICAL LIBRARY ARCHIVES
- WADE HAMPTON FROST: MEMO OF CONVERSATION WITH COL. RUSSELL, JULY 8, 1935 July 1935, 2 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-025)
  "FOUND IN HIS DESK AT HOME, IN ENVELOPE MARKED CONFIDENTIAL"
- LETTER FROM EDWARD S. GODFREY, JR., TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 21 Sept. 1938, 1 copy (Box-folder 09-026)
- LETTER FROM VICTOR G. HEISER TO WADE HAMPTON FROST 7 Nov. 1916, 2 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-027)
- LETTERS FROM WILLIAM H. HOWELL TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 1939-44, 17 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-028)
  "RE: FROST-HOWELL FAMILY RELATIONSHIP, AND SUSAN FROST PARRISH NOTES"
- LETTER FROM EDGAR E. HUME TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 20 May 1949, 2 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-029)
- LETTER FROM C. HAMPSON JONES TO WADE HAMPTON FROST late 1920s ?, 3 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-030)
- CORRESPONDENCE RE: JAMES P. LEAKE Feb. 1938-March 1973, 9 pp. copy; 1 ANS (Box-folder 09-031)
- LETTER FROM CHARLES T. MAITLAND TO WADE HAMPTON FROST 9 Sept. 1931, 4 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-032)
- LETTER FROM KENNETH F. MAXCY TO HARRIET FROST, SUSAN FROST PARRISH, AND SUSAN HAXALL FROST Oct. 1940-Oct. 1941, 8 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-033)
  MAXCY WAS EDITOR OF PAPERS OF WADE HAMPTON FROST
- CHARLES L. MINOR TO SUSAN FROST HAXALL 29 Apr. 1918, 2 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-034)
  RE: WADE HAMPTON FROST RETURN FROM SANATORIUM
- LETTER FROM HARRY S. MUSTARD TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 19 June 1965, 2 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-035)
  RE: FROST-MUSTARD TIES
- LETTER FROM SIR ARTHUR NEWSHOLME TO WADE HAMPTON FROST AND SUSAN HAXALL FROST July 1921-Sept. 1938, 22 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-036)
- LETTERS FROM JOHN W. OWENS TO WADE HAMPTON FROST, SUSAN HAXALL FROST, AND SUSAN FROST PARRISH Apr. 1936-Sept. 1941, 24 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-037)
- LETTERS FROM EDWARDS A. PARK TO WADE HAMPTON FROST, SUSAN HAXALL FROST, AND ERNEST L. STEBBINS Dec. 1933-May 1958, 10 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-038)
- LETTER FROM JOHN R. PAUL TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 2 Nov. 1956, 1 p. copy (Box-folder 09-039)
- LETTER FROM BARBARA S. QUIN TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 15 Oct. 1938, 1 p. copy (Box-folder 09-040)
- LETTERS FROM MILTON J. ROSENAU TO SUSAN PARRISH FROST Feb.-Apr. 1938, 6 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-041)
- LETTERS FROM WILLIAM T. SEDGWICK TO WADE HAMPTON FROST, SUSAN HAXALL FROST, AND MAY K. SEDGWICK Dec. 1914-Feb. 1921, 26 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-042)
- LETTERS FROM GEDDES SMITH TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST Jan. 1941-June 1943, 7 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-043)
- LETTER FROM GRAHAM R. TAYLOR TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 25 Jan. 1939, 2 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-044)
- LETTER FROM GRAHAM R. TAYLOR TO SUSAN PARRISH FROST 21 Aug. 1941, 1 p. copy (Box-folder 09-045)
- LETTERS FROM NEWTON F. WALKER TO WADE HAMPTON FROST Mar. 1923-Dec. 1926, 7 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-046)
- LETTER FROM FREDERIC C. WALCOTT TO WADE HAMPTON FROST 13 June 1934, 1 p. copy (Box-folder 09-047)
- LETTERS FROM WILLIAM H. WELCH TO WADE HAMPTON FROST, AND SUSAN HAXALL FROST Jan. 1929-Sept. 1933, 9 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-048)
- LETTER FROM J.M. WHEELIS, JR., TO WADE HAMPTON FROST 7 March 1938, 2 pp. copy (Box-folder 09-049)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST Jan.-Feb. 1938, 9 pp. copy; RESTRICTED ACCESS (Box-folder 09-050)
  TRANSCRIBED
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE 1921-83, 80 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-001)
  "WADE HAMPTON FROST, SUSAN HAXALL FROST, SUSAN FROST PARRISH"
- LETTERS FROM HUGH S. CUMMING TO WADE HAMPTON FROST March 1921-Feb. 1931, 17 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-002)
- LETTERS FROM HENRY FROST TO WADE HAMPTON FROST July 1913-Jan. 1917, 41 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-003)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO HENRY ROSE CARTER Feb. 1922-Aug. 1925, 34 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-004)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO LAURA ARMISTEAD CARTER July 1927-Sept. 1930, 16 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-005)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO HUGH S. CUMMING March 1921-Nov. 1929, 22 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-006)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO JOHN RAMEY AND MRS. JOHN S. RAMEY 1895-1898, 20 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-007)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 1920-1938, 13 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-008)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH Nov. 1937-Feb. 1938, 32 TM; 95 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-009)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST Jan.-Feb. 1938, 2 TM; 7 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-010)
- LETTERS FROM WADE HAMPTON FROST TO THOMAS LOWNDES FROST 1922-23, 29 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-011)
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN WADE HAMPTON FROST AND SUSAN HAXALL FROST AND WILLIAM H. WELCH July 1919-Aug. 1933, 25 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-012)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST: MEMO OF CONVERSATION WITH COL. RUSSELL, JULY 8, 1935 8 July 1935, 2 TM (Box-folder 10-013)
- LETTERS FROM WILLIAM H. HOWELL TO SUSAN FROST PARRISH 1939-44, 12 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-014)
- LETTERS FROM SIR ARTHUR NEWSHOLME TO WADE HAMPTON FROST AND SUSAN HAXALL FROST 1921-23, 7 TM; 12 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-015)
- LETTERS FROM WILLIAM T. SEDGWICK AND MARY K. SEDGWICK TO WADE HAMPTON FROST AND SUSAN HAXALL FROST 1914-21, 9 TM; 14 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-016)
- HENRY ROSE CARTER BIOGRAPHY, AND LETTER FROM WILLIAM H. WELCH TO WADE HAMPTON FROST 1929-34, 44 pp. copy (Box-folder 10-017)
- BOOKLET, "THEY ALSO SERVED MANKIND" PUBLISHED BY THE BALTIMORE CITY HEALTH DEPARTMENT 1955, 1 booklet (Box-folder 10-018)
  INCLUDES A BIOGRAPHY OF WADE HAMPTON FROST
- LETTER FROM SUSAN FROST PARRISH TO A. MCGEHEE HARVEY, AND A CHAPTER FROM HARVEY'S WORK ON WADE HAMPTON FROST 1984 Oct.-Nov., 1 TL (copy); 1 TM (copy) (Box-folder 10-019)
- PHOTOS FROM CHINA SENT TO WADE HAMPTON FROST BY REGINALD M. ATWATER 1921 (?), 5 photos B&W 1.5 x 2 (Box-folder 10-020)
- OBVERSE & REVERSE OF SEDGWICK MEMORIAL MEDAL AWARDED TO WADE HAMPTON FROST IN 1938 1938, 2 photos; 2 negatives B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 10-021)
- UNIDENTIFIED FROST FAMILY PHOTO nd, 1 negative (Box-folder 10-022)
- CARDS OF WADE HAMPTON FROST AS A MEMBER OF U.S. PUBLIC HEALTH AND MARINE HOSPITAL SERVICE n.d., 2 cards; 1.5 x 3.5 (Box-folder 10-023)
- REVEREND THOMAS FROST BY JOHN D. COGDILL 1806, 7 photos; 3 negatives B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 10-024)
- "FRANCIS LE JAU, D.D." 1665-1717, 3 photos; 1 negative B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 10-025)
  TAKEN FROM A PAINTING BY DR. JOHN B. IRVING
- OBITUARIES OF WADE HAMPTON FROST 1938, 6 newsclippings (copies) (Box-folder 10-026)
- OBITUARIES OF LOWELL J. REED 1966, 4 newsclippings (copies) (Box-folder 10-027)
- LETTER FROM SUSAN FROST PARRISH TO JOAN ECHTENKAMP KLEIN RE: DONATION OF WADE HAMPTON FROST PAPERS 1985, 1 TLS (Box-folder 10-028)
- ARTICLE ON WORK OF ERNEST L. STEBBINS OF JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY 1972 Dec., 1 newsclipping (copy) (Box-folder 10-029)
  FRIEND OF WADE HAMPTON FROST
- LETTER FROM VIRGINIA HAXALL HARRISON WHITRIDGE TO JACK GWALTNEY 1981 Dec., 2 TLS (copies) (Box-folder 10-030)
  RE DONATION OF $1000 FOR SUSAN F. PARRISH'S STAY/RESEARCH COSTS
- BOOKPLATES OF WADE HAMPTON FROST n.d., 1 bookplate; 1 TNS (copy) (Box-folder 10-031)
- ARTICLES ABOUT THE WORK OF WADE HAMPTON FROST 1938-76, 7 articles; 1 reprint (Box-folder 10-032)
- U. S. PUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE CINCINNATI STATION--STREAM POLLUTION INVESTIGATION ARTICLE 1913-16, 1 AN; 5 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-001)
- EXCERPT FROM A PROFILE OF THE UNITED STATES PUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE BY BESS FURMAN ON THE AMERICAN RED CROSS BUREAU OF SANITARY SERVICES, WWI, WADE HAMPTON FROST AS ORGANIZER 1917, 2 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-002)
- LETTERS FROM COL. JOHN L. MOSBY TO MRS. BOLLING W. HAXALL (1913-16) 1913-1975, 22 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-003)
  "CORRESPONDENCE OF SUSAN FROST PARRISH AND E. BERKELEY, JR., 1975 ABOUT HER GIFT TO ALDERMAN LIBRARY"
- DEATH OF LOWELL J. REED 1966 April, 3 pp. copies (newsclippings) (Box-folder 11-004)
- "IN BRIEF" ALUMNI ISSUES, JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND PUBLIC HEALTH 1971-73, 10 pp. journal clipping (Box-folder 11-005)
- NEWSCLIPPING ABOUT ERNEST L. STEBBINS' MEDICAL "PHILOSOPHY" 8 Dec. 1972, 1 newsclip (copy) (Box-folder 11-006)
  PUBLISHED IN THE BALTIMORE SUN
- INTERVIEW: DR. ANNA BAETJER, BY BARRY RUTIZER 24 June 1975, 5 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-007)
- INTERVIEW: DR. JAMES PERKINS, BY BARRY RUTIZER 27 June 1975, 6 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-008)
- INTERVIEW: DR. PHILIP SARTWELL, BY BARRY RUTIZER 25 June 1975, 10 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-009)
- INTERVIEW: DR. ERNEST L. STEBBINS, BY BARRY RUTIZER 24 June 1975, 4 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-010)
- WADE HAMPTON FROST MEMORABILIA FROM THE UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA 1898-1903, 13 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-011)
- LIST OF MEMORABILIA IN WADE HAMPTON FROST COLLECTION 1900-49, 1 AN; 11 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-012)
- FAMILY TREE OF WADE HAMPTON FROST nd, 3 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-013)
- PORTRAIT OF AN ENGLISH ANCESTOR OF WADE HAMPTON FROST ca. 1640, 1 AN; 2 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-014)
- THE FROST FAMILY IN ENGLAND AND AMERICA, WITH FULL BIBLIOGRAPHY 1909, 9 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-015)
- WALKER FAMILY OF SOUTH CAROLINA AND THEIR SCHOOL FOR DEAF AND BLIND 1849-1927, 6 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-016)
- THE PARISH LEAFLET (MEMORIAL TO DR. & MRS. HENRY FROST) May 1917, booklet (Box-folder 11-017)
- LETTER FROM FRANK R. FROST TO WADE HAMPTON FROST AND GENEAOLOGICAL INFORMATION 1 Feb. 1927, 7 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-018)
- HANDWRITTEN FAMILY TREE OF WADE HAMPTON FROST ca. 1932, 2 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-019)
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN HORACE C. FROST AND WADE HAMPTON FROST 1933-42, 10 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-020)
- NEWSCLIPPING: "200 YEAR OLD [NOLAND] HOUSE THAT WAS NEVER COMPLETED" n.d., 2 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-021)
- NEWSCLIPPINGS: BOLLING HAXALL HOUSE IN RICHMOND, NOTE ON POST-CIVIL WAR EDUCATION OF SONS n.d., 7 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-022)
- NEWSCLIPPING: "TRAVELERS' NOTES" ON REDLANDS," BY FRANK F. BEIRNE n.d., 2 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-023)
- NOLAND FAMILY TREE (PARTIAL) ca. 1950, 1 D; 8 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-024)
- HAXALL FAMILY TREE, FROM FAMILY RECORDS BY FRANK F. AND R.R. BEIRNE FOR HAXALL REUNION June 1931, 1 AD; 2 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-025)
- NEWSCLIPPINGS RE: DEATH OF WADE HAMPTON FROST May 1938, 3 newsclips w/AN; 3 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-026)
- ARTICLE: "SOME CONSIDERATIONS IN ESTIMATING THE SANITARY QUALITY OF WATER SUPPLIES" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST Dec. 1915, 24 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-027)
- ARTICLE DRAFT: "THE AMERICAN RED CROSS AS A PUBLIC HEALTH AUXILIARY" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 1917, 5 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-028)
- DRAFT OF MEMORANDUM: "GENERAL PROGRAM FOR CONSERVATION OF PUBLIC HEALTH IN THE CIVIL POPULATION DURING THE WAR" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 1917, 3 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-029)
- NEWSCLIPPING: WADE HAMPTON FROST APPOINTED HEAD OF DEPT. OF EPIDEMIOLOGY AND PUBLIC HEALTH ADMINISTRATION, JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND PUBLIC HEALTH 1921, 1 copy (Box-folder 11-030)
- ANNOUNCEMENT: CUTTER LECTURE ON PREVENTIVE MEDICINE AT HARVARD MEDICAL SCHOOL, BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 2-3 Feb. 1928, 1 copy (Box-folder 11-031)
- NEWSCLIPPINGS: GORDON BELL MEMORIAL LECTURE, WINNIPEG; "THE CHANGING ASPECT OF COMMUNICABLE DISEASES AND THEIR CONTROL", BY WADE HAMPTON FROST 13 Dec. 1929, 3 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-032)
- NEWSCLIPPING: "FROST MADE DEAN OF HYGIENE SCHOOL" AT JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY 1931, 1 copy (Box-folder 11-033)
- ARTICLE: "THE OUTLOOK FOR THE ERADICATION OF TUBERCULOSIS" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST Dec. 1935, 7 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-034)
- DRAFTS: "WHAT EVERY HEALTH OFFICER SHOULD KNOW" BY WADE HAMPTON FROST, FOR APHA MEETING, NEW YORK Oct. 1937, 9 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-035)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: MILBANK MEMORIAL FUND, BOUND BOOKLET 1938, 6 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-036)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: NEW YORK STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH, EDITORIAL 9 May 1938, 1 reprint (Box-folder 11-037)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: LIST OF CONTRIBUTORS TO FROST MEMORIAL FUND, WITH NOTE TO BARRY RUTIZER May-June 1938, 9 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-038)
  LIST IS PARTIAL
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: EDITORIAL, AMERICAN JOURNAL OF PUBLIC HEALTH, WITH DRAFT BY EDWARD GODFREY June 1938, 7 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-039)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: MARYLAND STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH MONTHLY BULLETIN, EDITORIAL June 1938, 1 reprint (Box-folder 11-040)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: HUMAN BIOLOGY MEMORIAL PHOTO Sept. 1938, 2 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-041)
  COPY GIVEN TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST BY DR. RAYMOND PEARL
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: KAPPA ALPHA JOURNAL EDITORIAL; LETTER FROM EDGAR E. HUME TO KENNETH F. MAXCY Nov. 1938, 3 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-042)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: RESOLUTION, JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY ALUMNI AT APHA MEETING, OCT. 1938; LETTER FROM ARCHIBALD DEAN TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 9 Nov. 1938, 1 copy (Box-folder 11-043)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: SEDGWICK MEMORIAL MEDAL COMMITTEE ANNOUNCEMENT, BY DR. HAVEN EMERSON AT APHA MEETING, OCT. 1938, FROM AMERICAN JOURNAL OF PUBLIC HEALTH Nov. 1938, 2 D; 5 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-044)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: COMMONWEALTH FUND ANNUAL REPORT; MEMORIAL PHOTO, PRESENTED TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST BY FUND Jan. 1939, 9 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-045)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: ADDRESS BY WILLIAM HENRY HOWELL ON PRESENTATION OF PORTRAIT OF WADE HAMPTON FROST TO JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY AT COMMENCEMENT June 1939, 2 TD; 3 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-046)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: ANNUAL REPORT OF BALTIMORE CITY HEALTH DEPARTMENT 27 Oct. 1939, 4 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-047)
  WITH LETTER FROM DR. WILLIAMS TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: "PANUM'S "OBSERVATIONS MADE DURING THE EPIDEMIC OF MEASLES ON THE FAROE ISLANDS IN 1846", DEDICATED TO WADE HAMPTON FROST 16 July 1940, 8 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-048)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: "PUBLIC HEALTH BALLOONS," EDITORIAL BY H.S. MUSTARD, AMERICAN JOURNAL OF PUBLIC HEALTH Sept. 1941, 1 reprint; 3 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-049)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: FOLIO OF MEMORIAL TRIBUTES TO WADE HAMPTON FROST ON 10TH ANNIVERSARY OF HIS DEATH, PRESENTED TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST 1 May 1948, 37 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-050)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: MAZYCK RAVENEL ON "PAPERS OF WADE HAMPTON FROST" IN AMERICAN JOURNAL OF PUBLIC HEALTH Nov. 1941, 5 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-051)
  ARTICLE
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: "A GREAT EPIDEMIOLOGIST", FROM BRITISH MEDICAL JOURNAL, WITH LETTER TO SUSAN HAXALL FROST FROM LEWIS THOMPSON 3 Oct. 1942, 2 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-052)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: VIRGINIA MEDICAL MONTHLY, EDITORIAL, "DOCTORS FOR WHOM THE PUBLIC SHOULD BE THANKFUL" Dec. 1950, 4 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-053)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: "THE GREAT PIONEERS OF PUBLIC HEALTH" BY WILSON SMILLIE, ET AL. Sept. 1953, 1 reprint; 7 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-054)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: "THEY ALSO SERVED MANKIND"; MEMORIAL BOOKLET PRESENTED AT DEDICATION OF EASTERN HEALTH DISTRICT BUILDING, BALTIMORE 17 Jan. 1955, 15 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-055)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: ERNEST L. STEBBINS' MEMORIAL "LETTER TO FORMER STUDENTS AND FRIENDS OF DR. WADE HAMPTON FROST" 1 May 1958, 8 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-056)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: ANNUAL WADE HAMPTON FROST LECTURES, APHA 1973, 1 reprint w/AN (Box-folder 11-057)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: REED-FROST SYMPOSIUM 30 April 1976, 2 brochures; 18 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-058)
- POSTHUMOUS HONORS: PUBLIC HEALTH REPORTS Sept.-Oct. 1980, 3 pp. copies (Box-folder 11-059)
- LETTER FROM S.F. PARRISH TO A. MCGEHEE HARVEY Oct. 1984, 1 copy (Box-folder 11-060)
- MISCELLANEOUS MATERIAL ON HENRY R. FROST, SURGEON, C.S.A. nd, 70 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-001)
- HENRY R. FROST, SURGEON, C.S.A. PUBLICATIONS 1795-1866, 52 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-002)
- MISCELLANEOUS MATERIAL ON LE JAU, PARKER, AND FROST FAMILIES 1836-1938, 10 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-003)
- MISCELLANEOUS MATERIAL ON FROST-SINKLER FAMILIES nd, 15 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-004)
- MISCELLANEOUS MATERIAL ON DOWNES, GEDDINGS, AND LYNCH FAMILIES n.d., 21 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-005)
- FROST FAMILY TREE 1450-1986, 6 AM; 1 brochure; 8 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-006)
- FAMILY HISTORY OF WADE H. FROST 1927-1986, 16 AM; 6 TM; 35 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-007)
- WALKER FAMILY OF SOUTH CAROLINA AND THEIR SCHOOL FOR THE DEAF & BLIND 1849-1927, 2 AN; 1 newsclipping; 44 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-008)
- MISCELLANEOUS MATERIAL ON FROST FAMILY HISTORY 1909, 2 AN; 80 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-009)
  NOTES ATTACHED
- ARTICLE BY THOMAS G. FROST AND EDWARD L. FROST "THE FROST FAMILY IN ENGLAND AND AMERICA" 1909, 35 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-010)
- PHOTOCOPY AND CORRESPONDENCE RE: SILVER INKSTAND: THE SCHULDHAM PLATE n.d., 14 pp. copies; 2 AN (Box-folder 12-011)
- NOTES BY SUSAN FROST PARRISH ON FROST-HORRY BIBLE n.d., 3 AN (Box-folder 12-012)
- "THE PARISH LEAFLET"--FAUQUIER COUNTY, VA May 1917, 1 leaflet (Box-folder 12-013)
- "SOME MEMORIES, OR LAST SUMMER'S CLOUDS" BY FRANK R. FROST 1922, 48 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-014)
- PARKER FAMILY RECORDS AND NOTES 1670-1935, 80 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-015)
- BROUN FAMILY OF SOUTH CAROLINA 1971, 40 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-016)
- OWINGS-LESESNE FAMILY HISTORIES n.d., 15 pp. copies (Box-folder 12-017)
- ANCESTRAL TABLETS: FROST FAMILY TREE 1936, 1 book (Box-folder 12-018)
- SUSAN FROST PARRISH RESEARCH/TRAVEL RECORDS 1986, 10 AN; 15 TD (Box-folder 13-001)
- MISCELLANEOUS MATERIAL RE: HARRY S. MUSTARD "1959, 1985", "articles, obits (16 copies)" (Box-folder 13-002)
- MISCELLANEOUS MATERIAL RE: CAMBRIDGE UNIVERSITY 1986, articles (80 pp. copies) (Box-folder 13-003)